[
    {
    "option1": "I could going.",
    "option2": "I could gone.",
    "option3": "I could go.",
    "option4": "I can go.",
    "question": "আমি যেতে পারতাম",
    "correct": 3,
    "isPicture": false
    },
    {
    "option1": "Could I go ?",
    "option2": "Could I goes ?",
    "option3": "Can I go ?",
    "option4": "Could I going ?",
    "question": "আমি কি যেতে পারতাম ?",
    "correct": 1,
    "isPicture": false
    },
    {
    "option1": "I can not go.",
    "option2": "I could not going.",
    "option3": "I could not go.",
    "option4": "I could not gone.",
    "question": "আমি যেতে পারলাম না",
    "correct": 3,
    "isPicture": false
    },
    {
    "option1": "Perhaps I can go.",
    "option2": "Perhaps I shall gone.",
    "option3": "Perhaps I shall go.",
    "option4": "Perhaps I will go.",
    "question": "আমি বোধহয় যাবো",
    "correct": 3,
    "isPicture": false
    },
    {
    "option1": "I was thinking of going.",
    "option2": "I was thinking of go.",
    "option3": "I was thinking of gone.",
    "option4": "I thinking of going.",
    "question": "আমি যাবো ভাবছিলাম",
    "correct": 1,
    "isPicture": false
    },
    {
    "option1": "I have to gone.",
    "option2": "I have to going.",
    "option3": "I has to go.",
    "option4": "I have to go.",
    "question": "আমায় যেতে হবে",
    "correct": 4,
    "isPicture": false
    },
    {
    "option1": "Shall I have to going ?",
    "option2": "Shall I have to go ?",
    "option3": "Shall I have go ?",
    "option4": "Will I have to go ?",
    "question": "আমায় কি যেতে হবে ?",
    "correct": 2,
    "isPicture": false
    },
    {
    "option1": "Shall I not have  go ?",
    "option2": "Shall I not has to go ?",
    "option3": "Shall I not have to go ?",
    "option4": "Will I not have to go ?",
    "question": "আমায় কি যেতে হবে না ?",
    "correct": 3,
    "isPicture": false
    },
    {
    "option1": "I need to gone.",
    "option2": "I need to go.",
    "option3": "I need to going.",
    "option4": "I am to going.",
    "question": "আমার যাবার দরকার",
    "correct": 2,
    "isPicture": false
    },
    {
    "option1": "Why shall I go ?",
    "option2": "Why shall I went ?",
    "option3": "Why shall I going ?",
    "option4": "Why will I go ?",
    "question": "আমি কেন যাবো ?",
    "correct": 1,
    "isPicture": false
    },
    {
    "option1": "Why will I not go ?",
    "option2": "Why shall I not going ?",
    "option3": "Why shall I not go ?",
    "option4": "Why can I not go ?",
    "question": "কেন আমি যাবো না ?",
    "correct": 3,
    "isPicture": false
    },
    {
    "option1": "When shall I go ?",
    "option2": "When shall I gone ?",
    "option3": "When can I go ?",
    "option4": "When will I go ?",
    "question": "আমি কখন যাবো ?",
    "correct": 1,
    "isPicture": false
    },
    {
    "option1": "Where shall I gone ?",
    "option2": "Where can I go ?",
    "option3": "Where shall I go ?",
    "option4": "Where shall I going ?",
    "question": "আমি কোথায় যাবো ?",
    "correct": 3,
    "isPicture": false
    },
    {
    "option1": "With who shall I go ?",
    "option2": "With whom shall I go ?",
    "option3": "With whom shall I went ?",
    "option4": "With whom will I go ?",
    "question": "আমি কার সঙ্গে যাবো ?",
    "correct": 2,
    "isPicture": false
    },
    {
    "option1": "I want to goes.",
    "option2": "I want to gone.",
    "option3": "I want to go.",
    "option4": "I want going.",
    "question": "আমি যেতে চাই",
    "correct": 3,
    "isPicture": false
    },
    {
    "option1": "I love to gone.",
    "option2": "I can go.",
    "option3": "I have to go.",
    "option4": "I love to go.",
    "question": "আমার যেতে ভালো লাগে",
    "correct": 4,
    "isPicture": false
    },
    {
    "option1": "I wish to go.",
    "option2": "I wish to goes.",
    "option3": "I wishes to go.",
    "option4": "I wish go.",
    "question": "আমার যাবার ইচ্ছে  আছে",
    "correct": 1,
    "isPicture": false
    },
    {
    "option1": "If I could gone !",
    "option2": "If I can go !",
    "option3": "If I could go !",
    "option4": "If I can goes !",
    "question": "আমি যদি যেতে পারতাম !",
    "correct": 3,
    "isPicture": false
    }
]